Finding Aid for Books published for the use of the Bay View Reading Club, 1887-1914
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Books published for the use of the Bay View Reading Club 1887-1914
Bay View Reading Club.
1 linear foot
2009141 Aa 2
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The provenance of this collection is unknown.
No further additions to the collection are expected.
The collection is open to research.
The Bay View Reading Club was a program of the Bay View Association. Also known as the Bay View Reading Circle, the club flourished in the period of 1893-1921.
This is a collection of books published for the use of the Bay View Reading Club. The books have been listed alphabetically by author.
Subjects:
Group reading--Michigan.
- Books published for the use of the Bay View Reading Club
  - Boulger, Demetrious C. Belgium. 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bryce, James. South America: Observations and Impressions. 1912 (Macmillan) (Box 1)
  - Carson, W. E. Mexico: The Wonderland of the South. 1913 (Macmillan) (Box 1)
  - Clough, Ethlyn T., ed. Africa: An Account of Past and Contemporary Conditions and Progress. 1911 (Box 1)
  - Clough, Ethlyn T., Norwegian Life: An Account of Past and Contemporary Conditions and Progress in Norway and Sweden. 1909 (Box 1)
  - Clough, Ethlyn T., Oriental Life: An Account of Past and Contemporary Conditions and Progress in Asia, Excepting China, India and Japan. 1910 (Box 1)
  - Clough, Ethlyn T., South American Life: An Account of Past and Contemporary Conditions and Progress in South America. 1912 (Box 1)
  - Compton, Herbert. Indian Life in Town and Country. 1904 (Putnam's ) (Box 1)
  - Dowden, Edward. A History of French Literature. 1898 (Appleton) (Box 1)
  - Griffis, William Elliot. Brave Little Holland, and What She Has Taught Us. Revised ed. 1894 (Houghton Mifflin) (Box 1)
  - Hall, John M., ed. England: An Account of Past and Contemporary Conditions and Progress. 1906 (Box 1)
  - Hall, John M., ed. England: An Account of Past and Contemporary Conditions and Progress. Reprint. 1914 (Box 1)
  - Hall, John M., Greek Life. 1908 (Box 1)
  - Hall, John M., United States. 1907 (Box 1)
  - Hawtrey, Mrs. H.C. A Short History of Germany. 1913 (Box 1)
  - Higgin, L. Spanish Life in Town and Country. 1902 (Putnam's) (Box 1)
  - Hoppin, James M. Old England. 1900 (Houghton Mifflin) (Box 1)
  - Lummis, Charles F. The Awakening of a Nation: Mexico of Today. 1902 (Harper) (Box 1)
  - Martin, W.A.P. The Awakening of China. 1910 (Doubleday, Page) (Box 1)
  - Palmer, Francis H.E. Austro-Hungarian Life in Town and Country. 1903 (Putnam's) (Box 1)
  - Parmalee, Mary Platt. Evolution of an Empire: A Brief Historical Sketch of the United States. 1896 (Harison) (Box 1)
  - Parmalee, Mary Platt. A Short History of France. 1905 (Scribner's) (Box 1)
  - Parmalee, Mary Platt. A Short History of France. Revised ed. 1908 (Scribner's) (Box 1)
  - Parmalee, Mary Platt. A Short History of Germany. 1897 (Harison) (Box 1)
  - Parmalee, Mary Platt. A Short History of Rome and Italy. 1901 (Scribner's) (Box 1)
  - Parmalee, Mary Platt. A Short History of Rome and Italy. 1908 (Scribner's) (Box 1)
  - Parmalee, Mary Platt. A Short History of Russia. 1899 (Continental), 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Parmalee, Mary Platt. The Story of Spain Briefly Told. 1898 (Continental), 3 copies (Box 1)
  - Parry, Emma Louise. Life Among the Germans. 1887 (Lathrop) (Box 1)
  - Stoddard, Charles Augustus. Across Russia: From the Baltic to the Danube. 1891 (Scribner's) (Box 1)
  - Witt, Robert Clermont. How to Look at Pictures. 1905 (Box 1)